http://www.rvcu.org/privacy/

FACTS
What does River Valley Credit Union do with your personal information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
Payment history and transaction or loss history
Overdraft history and checking account information
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons River Valley Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does River Valley share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes —
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Questions?
Call 515-232-1654 or go to www.rvcu.org
Who is providing this notice?
River Valley Credit Unioin
What we do
How does River Valley Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or apply for a loan
make a wire transfer or use your credit or debit card
make deposits or withdrawals from your account
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
River Valley Credit Union has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
River Valley Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies.
© 2020 River Valley Credit Union. All rights reserved.
Privacy PolicySitemap
WEB DEVELOPMENT BY
GLOBAL REACH
Back to Top
© 2020 River Valley Credit Union. All rights reserved.
